kind of like lost our fervor for education and the tool for liberation that it is saw a story
of a guy in texas who was actually being charged uh with a felony and like there's like time
possibly attached to him creating a zine someone was transporting his zines and got arrested at a
protest and they attached that they were transporting the zines to the arrest okay the
fact that they're like accrediting whoever it was in texas to the equivalent of like carrying
contraband yes or what the accreditation was yeah it goes back to and that's why i think it's
understated like how much we fought for education to get it to where to where it is how how much of
a criminal act it was especially on the plantations to find a slave that was reading that
was able to you know discern these things that are going on i think that's something that we've lost
we now have gotten to a space where it's like oh if you have money or if you have some like notoriety
these are the things that we um desire um and so that's already an attempt to crack down on the
spaces that people are going to eventually go back to once these spaces are no longer uh available
and i would also add that when you came on last time and you were talking about us and what they're
building in memphis yeah all of that ends up connecting because that is attached to ai ai is now
going to render these apps maybe a bit alarmist but you're not going to be able to know what's real or
not yeah and i mean i don't think that's um hyperbolic in any sense or any capacity you know that
where'd you get the information from because now you look something up on google the first thing that
comes up is the ai overview and people just take that to be gospel and i'm like well what's the
source you know let's check let's see what their credentials are because there are people behind
these algorithms that have their own vested interests um and it's those lines that you're
talking about in